<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>PixelSarab</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://pixelsarab.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-10-15T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://pixelsarab.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Neil Messelmani</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unity Games</title>
    <link href="http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Unity-Games/"/>
    <id>http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Unity-Games/</id>
    <published>2018-10-15T15:19:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-10-15T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here are a couple of projects I made with Unity, they showcase some game design and concepts. Game dev is a passion of mine, so you will see more of them here, and more devlogs as well. All my code is MIT licenced and will be on Github. </p><p>Orbit:<br>This is a tiny game where you need to put a satellite in a way where it will stay in orbit and does not crush into a planet.<br><a href="https://github.com/kishikaisei/Games/tree/master/Orbit" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Github’s link to Orbit’s Scripts</a></p><p>Obstacles:<br>This is a small test on pathfinding and steering behaviour, not much animation is here, as it is more of a test, than a product.</p><p><a href="https://github.com/kishikaisei/Games/tree/master/Obsacles" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Github’s link to Obstacles’s Scripts</a></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      Here are a couple of projects I made with Unity, they showcase some game design and concepts. Game dev is a passion of mine, so you will see more of them here, and more devlogs as well. All my code is MIT licenced and will be on Github. 

Orbit:
This is a tiny game where you need to put a satellite 
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Projects" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Projects/"/>
    
      <category term="Development" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Development/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>chouf</title>
    <link href="http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/chouf/"/>
    <id>http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/chouf/</id>
    <published>2018-10-14T18:04:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-10-14T21:46:20.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I worked with some cool people on a documentary about a couple where both of them are blind. I did the set the subtitles and co-worked on the video editing.</p><iframe width="100%" height="600" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XV4Ph5OAuYs" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      I worked with some cool people on a documentary about a couple where both of them are blind. I did the set the subtitles and co-worked on the video editing.
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Projects" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Projects/"/>
    
      <category term="Video-Editing" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Video-Editing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Vimming</title>
    <link href="http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Vimming/"/>
    <id>http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Vimming/</id>
    <published>2018-10-11T12:45:42.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-10-12T22:50:54.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="nvim.png" alt="nvim.png"></p><p>Having a passion for code, I always search for the best tools I can use to optimise my workflow, and overall enjoyment of coding.</p><p>Havig a good editor, with a nice colorscheme, and a nice font, will make the experience of coding even more fun than the problem solving that is inherited by code.<br>I checked out all sorts of IDEs and text editors, I enjoyed some, I had hard time with others, like PyCharm and Emacs respectively, Emacs is amazing but the learning curve is very steep for me, and I don’t have that much time to learn the intriquecies of an OS of a text editor.<br>In the end, I found VIM, I fell in love with its flexibility, it was weird at first, but fun. It was fun to create the .vimrc file and installing helpfull plug-ins.</p><script src="https://gist.github.com/kishikaisei/77a062e208defb5e9d9adac06c5bc329.js"></script>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      In the end, I found VIM, I fell in love with its flexibility, it was weird at first, but fun. It was fun to create the .vimrc file and installing helpfull plug-ins.
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Development" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Development/"/>
    
      <category term="Tools" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Tools/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Hello-World/"/>
    <id>http://pixelsarab.com/2018/10/Hello-World/</id>
    <published>2018-10-10T23:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-10-11T21:25:26.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[ I’m Neil Messelmani, I am Czech-Tunisian with love for Development and experience in Project/Team Managment. <p>I have worked in a multinational corporation, so that implies that we worked cross time-zones, which was challenging. I started there as Production Designer, which consisted in localising assets. I took every new project opportunity, proving my versatility within the organization, which consisted on needs at the time with no individual to work on it, they were mostly in-house softwares which I need to learn and be profiscient at quickly, I pride myself on being a fast learner.<br>I helped with IT technicalities as well, which ranges from hardware setup to script development and software setup. I also led in engagement activities, like paper airplane origami challenge and miscelaneous games. In the end I opened the market for retouching on site, and finally expaned my team..<br>As a senior my responsibilities were in leadership, project management, and doing design work, which was mostly retouching. Even though I was a retoucher, I implemented development as often as I can. That meant scripting photoshop to automate the tedious export process, and a tool that fetches data from a database and creats photoshop documents based on the fetched data.<br>Also in cimpress there were a training for first aid which I took.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      I’m Neil Messelmani, I am Czech-Tunisian with love for Development and experience in Project/Team Managment.
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Miscelaneous" scheme="http://pixelsarab.com/tags/Miscelaneous/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
